Register of the Milan Gavrilović Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Incremental Materials of 1994., 1940-1942, undated. (Reel 66, Box 53-54)
  - Yugoslav Legation in Moscow, 1940-1942 (Reel 66, Folder 53-54)
    - Financial records, personnel and office expenses, 1940-1941 (Reel 66, Box-folder 53: 2-3)
    - Financial records of household goods sold in May, 1941 (Reel 66, Box-folder 54: 1)
    - Receipts, Kujbiev, 1941-1942 (Reel 66, Box-folder 54: 2)
  - Untitled, incomplete manuscript relating to Yugoslav political situation, undated (Box-folder 54: 3, Reel 66)
- Photographs, n.d. (Reading room workstation, Photo-file Photo file)
  69 prints depicting Milan Gavrilović and others, including Branislaw Stanišić
  - 14 prints depicting Milan Gavrilović and others (Photo-file A)
  - 16 prints depicting unidentified individuals, family members, and various homes (Photo-file B)
  - 28 prints depicting various individuals associated with Milan Gavrilović (Photo-file C)
  - 11 prints depicting Branislav M. Stanišić (Photo-file D)